Finding Aid for Bureau of Government Library (University of Michigan) records, 1935-1980
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Clippings
  - S-Z
    - Teachers 1953-1977, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Teachers' Salaries 1955-1972 (Box 28)
    - Time 1966-1975 (Box 28)
    - Toll Roads 1953-1958, 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Tourist Trade 1929-1971, 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Township Government
      - DeWitt Township 1965-1967 (Box 29)
      - Delhi Township 1962-1968 (Box 29)
      - Delta Township (Ingham County) 1961-1967 (Box 29)
      - Lansing Township 1962-1978 (Box 29)
      - Meridian Township (Ingham County) 1959-1967 (Box 29)
      - Ypsilanti Township 1957-1964 (Box 29)
      - Washtenaw County 1943-1962, 3 folders (Box 29)
      - Macomb County 1962 (Box 29)
      - Redford Township, circa 1962 (Box 29)
      - Royal Oak Township 1956 (Box 29)
    - Township Planning 1956-1962 (Box 29)
    - Trading Stamps 1956-1966 (Box 29)
    - Traffic Regulations
      - Ann Arbor 1952-1977 (Box 29)
      - Detroit 1938-1962 (Box 29)
      - Michigan 1935-1979, 3 folders (Box 29)
      - Lansing 1953-1967 (Box 29)
    - Traffic Surveys 1953-1960 (Box 29)
    - Trailers 1942-1975 (Box 29)
    - Training
      - Ann Arbor 1964-1970 (Box 29)
      - Detroit Area 1964-1970 (Box 29)
      - Lansing Area 1964 (Box 29)
      - Michigan 1936-1967 (Box 29)
    - Transportation
      - Ann Arbor 1951-1980, 4 folders (Box 29)
      - Detroit 1938-1980, 9 folders (Box 29)
      - Lansing 1952-1976 (Box 29)
      - Michigan 1941-1980, 4 folders (Box 29)
      - Ypsilanti 1962 (Box 29)
    - Travel Regulations 1958-1967 (Box 29)
    - Unemployment 1935-1950, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Unemployment Compensation 1935-1980, 6 folders (Box 30)
    - U. S. Congress 1960-1980, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - U. S. President 1976 (Box 30)
    - Vocational Education 1963-1976 (Box 30)
    - Voting
      - Ann Arbor 1948-1979 (Box 30)
      - Detroit 1934-1979 (Box 30)
      - Lansing and Ingham County 1956-1970 (Box 30)
      - Michigan 1944-1979, 4 folders (Box 30)
      - Washtenaw County 1961-1979 (Box 30)
    - War Memorials 1950-1952 (Box 30)
    - War Veterans 1943-1974, 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Water Carriers 1958 (Box 30)
    - Water Supply
      - Ann Arbor and Washtenaw County 1941-1980, 11 folders (Box 30)
      - Detroit Area 1945-1979, 3 folders (Box 31)
      - Flint 1964 (Box 31)
      - Grand Rapids 1953-1960 (Box 31)
      - Grand River Valley 1960-1964 (Box 31)
      - Great Lakes Area 1955-1962 (Box 31)
      - Huron River Valley 1956-1980, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Ingham County 1960-1980 (Box 31)
      - Lansing (metropolitan area) 1953-1980 (Box 31)
      - Oakland County 1955-1958 (Box 31)
      - Washtenaw County Area 1969 (Box 31)
      - Ypsilanti 1949-1964 (Box 31)
    - Waterways
      - General 1954-1979, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Great Lakes Area 1956-1974 (Box 31)
      - Michigan 1941-1980, 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Willow Village 1946-1966 (Box 31)
    - Workmen's Compensation 1937-1980, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Women 1962-1979 (Box 31)
    - Youth Problems
      - Ann Arbor 1964-1974 (Box 31)
      - Detroit 1950-1969 (Box 31)
      - Lansing 1951-1965 (Box 31)
      - Michigan 1950-1980 (Box 31)
    - Zoning
      - Ann Arbor 1950-1977, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Detroit 1940-1964 (Box 31)
      - Groveland Township undated (Box 31)
      - Huron Township 1958 (Box 31)
      - Lansing 1964-1979 (Box 31)
      - Livonia 1952-1953 (Box 31)
      - Michigan 1939-1979 (Box 31)
      - Washtenaw County 1941-1969 (Box 31)
- Pamphlets
  - A-E
    - Abortion (Box 32)
    - Accident Prevention (Box 32)
    - Accounting -- State of Michigan (Box 32)
    - Administrative Management (Box 32)
    - Agriculture, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Air Pollution (Box 32)
    - Airports (Box 32)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 32)
    - Annexation of Territory (Box 32)
    - Assessments
      - Michigan (Box 32)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 32)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 32)
      - Flint (Box 32)
    - Associations -- Citizens Research Council of Michigan (Box 32)
    - Banks and Banking (Box 32)
    - Beverage Containers (Box 32)
    - Bibliographies (Box 32)
    - Boats and Boating (Box 32)
    - Bonds (Box 32)
    - Budget Administration (Box 32)
    - Budgets
      - Municipal
        - Ann Arbor (Box 32)
        - Detroit (Box 32)
      - State (Box 32)
    - Building (Box 32)
    - Building Laws
      - Ann Arbor (Box 32)
      - Michigan (Box 32)
    - Business (Box 32)
    - Charities (Box 32)
    - Charters
      - Michigan (Box 33)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 33)
      - Detroit (Box 33)
    - Child Welfare (Box 33)
    - Cities and Towns
      - Michigan (Box 33)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 33)
      - Detroit (Box 33)
      - Planning
        - Michigan (Box 33)
        - Ann Arbor (Box 33)
        - Detroit, 6 folders (Box 33)
        - Carleton (Box 34)
        - Cheboygan (Box 34)
        - Clawson (Box 34)
        - East Lansing (Box 34)
        - Inkster (Box 34)
        - Kalamazoo (Box 34)
        - Oak Park (Box 34)
        - Plymouth (Box 34)
        - Saginaw (Box 34)
        - Wayne (Box 34)
    - Civic Organizations (Box 35)
      - Michigan (Box 35)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 35)
    - Civil Defense
      - Michigan (Box 35)
      - Ann Arbor and Washtenaw County (Box 35)
    - Civil Rights (Box 35)
    - Civil Service
      - Municipal (Box 35)
      - State, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Colleges and Universities
      - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - University of Michigan, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Finance (Box 35)
    - Community and College -- Ann Arbor (Box 35)
    - Community Development
      - Saginaw (Box 35)
      - Michigan (Box 35)
    - Community Surveys
      - Michigan (Box 35)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 35)
      - Detroit (Box 35)
      - Whitmore Lake (Box 35)
    - Conflict of Interest (Box 35)
    - Constitutional Conventions (Box 36)
      - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Bibliographies, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Constitutions -- State -- Michigan, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Consumers Credit (Box 36)
    - Consumers Protection (Box 36)
    - Coroners (Box 36)
    - Corrections (Box 36)
    - Councils, Municipal -- Ann Arbor (Box 36)
    - County Government
      - Michigan (Box 36)
      - Kalamazoo County (Box 36)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 36)
      - Wayne County (Box 36)
    - County Planning (Box 37)
      - Michigan (Box 37)
      - Alger County (Box 37)
      - Baraga County (Box 37)
      - Eaton County (Box 37)
      - Washtenaw County, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Courts
      - Michigan (Box 37)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 37)
      - Wayne County (Box 37)
    - Credit Unions (Box 37)
    - Crime and Criminals
      - Michigan (Box 37)
      - Wayne County (Box 37)
      - Detroit (Box 37)
    - Debts (Box 37)
    - Directories (Box 37)
    - Disabilities (Box 37)
    - Discrimination in Employment (Box 37)
    - Economic Conditions
      - Michigan Detroit Washtenaw County (Box 37)
    - Economic Planning (Box 37)
    - Education (Box 38)
      - Michigan (Box 38)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 38)
      - Finance
        - Michigan (Box 38)
        - Detroit (Box 38)
    - Elections
      - State (Washtenaw County) (Box 38)
      - Local (Box 38)
      - County (Box 38)
      - State (Michigan) (Box 38)
      - Municipal
        - Michigan (Box 38)
        - Ann Arbor (Box 38)
        - Detroit (Box 38)
      - Funds (Box 39)
    - Employment
      - Michigan, 5 folders (Box 39)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 39)
      - Battle Creek (Box 39)
      - Bay City (Box 39)
      - Detroit (Box 39)
      - Jackson (Box 39)
      - Kalamazoo (Box 39)
      - Lansing (Box 39)
      - Muskegon (Box 39)
      - Saginaw (Box 39)
    - Expenditures -- State (Box 39)
    - Environment (Box 39)
  - F-M
    - Federal Aid (Box 39)
    - Finance
      - State
        - Michigan (Box 40)
        - Bibliography (Box 40)
      - Local, 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Municipal
        - Michigan (Box 40)
        - Ann Arbor, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Detroit (Box 40)
    - Fiscal Administration (Box 40)
    - Forest and Forestry (Box 41)
    - Gas Manufacture and Works (Box 41)
    - Governmental Research Bureaus
      - Michigan (Box 41)
      - Detroit (Box 41)
    - Harbors (Box 41)
    - Highways (Box 41)
    - History (Box 41)
    - Home Rule (Box 41)
    - Hospitals (Box 41)
    - Housing
      - General (Box 41)
      - Michigan, 3 folders (Box 41)
      - Ann arbor (Box 42)
      - Benzie County (Box 42)
      - Livingston County (Box 42)
      - Wayne County (Box 42)
      - Detroit (Box 42)
      - Flint (Box 42)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 42)
      - Kalamazoo (Box 42)
    - Income
      - Michigan (Box 42)
      - Detroit (Box 42)
    - Indians (Box 42)
    - Industrial Districts (Box 42)
    - Information Processing Systems
      - Michigan (Box 42)
      - Municipal -- Ann Arbor (Box 42)
    - Initiative and Referendum (Box 42)
    - Insurance
      - Governmental (Box 42)
      - Health (Box 42)
      - Motor Vehicle (Box 42)
    - Intergovernmental Relations
      - Washtenaw County (Box 42)
      - Michigan (Box 42)
    - Intergovernmental Tax Relation
      - Wayne County (Box 42)
      - Ann arbor (Box 42)
    - Judges (Box 42)
    - Juvenile Courts (Box 42)
    - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 42)
    - Labor Administration (Box 42)
    - Labor and Laboring Classes (Box 42)
    - Land Subdivision
      - Michigan (Box 42)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 42)
      - Oakland County (Box 43)
    - Land Use
      - Michigan (Box 43)
      - Lyon Township (Box 43)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 43)
    - Lawyers (Box 43)
    - Laws, Statutes, etc. (Box 43)
    - League of Women Voters (Box 43)
    - Legislatures
      - Michigan (Box 43)
      - Apportionment (Box 43)
    - Libraries
      - University of Michigan (Box 43)
      - Michigan (Box 43)
    - Licenses (Box 43)
    - Liquor (Box 43)
    - Local Government (Box 43)
    - Location of Industry (Box 43)
    - Maps
      - Michigan (Box 43)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 43)
    - Medical Care (Box 43)
    - Mental Health (Box 43)
    - Metropolitan Planning (Box 44)
      - Detroit (Box 44)
      - Flint (Box 44)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 44)
      - Michigan (Box 44)
      - Muskegon (Box 44)
    - Michigan (Box 44)
    - Migrants (Box 44)
    - Minorities
      - Michigan (Box 44)
      - Detroit (Box 44)
    - Mobile Homes (Box 44)
    - Motor Busses (Box 44)
    - Motor Vehicles
      - Michigan (Box 44)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 44)
      - Detroit (Box 44)
    - Motor Vehicle Drivers (Box 44)
    - Municipal Government
      - Michigan (Box 44)
      - Ann Arbor, 3 folders (Box 44)
      - Allegan (Box 45)
      - Birmingham and Bronson (Box 45)
      - Clawson (Box 45)
      - Detroit (Box 45)
      - Ecorse (Box 45)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 45)
      - Grosse Pointe Park (Box 45)
      - Holland (Box 45)
      - Jackson (Box 45)
      - Kalamazoo (Box 45)
      - Livonia (Box 45)
      - Madison Heights (Box 45)
      - Marquette (Box 45)
      - Marysville (Box 45)
      - Oak Park (Box 45)
      - Pontiac (Box 45)
      - River Rouge (Box 45)
      - Royal Oak (Box 45)
      - Saginaw (Box 45)
      - Wixom (Box 45)
      - Wyoming (Box 45)
    - Municipal Government Manager Plan (Box 45)
    - Municipal Incorporation (Box 45)
    - Municipal League (Box 45)
    - Municipal Services (Box 45)
  - N-S
    - Narcotics (Box 45)
    - Natural Resources (Box 45)
    - Negroes (Box 45)
    - Occupations (Box 45)
    - Old Age
      - Michigan (Box 45)
      - Housing (Box 45)
    - Ordinances (Box 45)
    - Parking
      - Michigan (Box 45)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 45)
      - Detroit (Box 45)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 45)
      - Lansing (Box 45)
      - Jackson (Box 45)
    - Parks (Box 45)
    - Pension -- Civil (Box 46)
      - Michigan (Box 46)
      - Detroit, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Personnel Administration
      - Michigan (Box 46)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 46)
      - Ingham County (Box 46)
      - Service Ratings (Box 46)
      - Suggestions
        - Michigan (Box 46)
        - Ann Arbor (Box 46)
      - Work Terms (Box 46)
    - Planning (Box 46)
    - Plumbing (Box 46)
    - Police
      - Michigan (Box 46)
      - Ann arbor (Box 46)
      - Detroit (Box 46)
      - Lansing (Box 46)
      - State (Box 46)
    - Political Parties (Box 46)
    - Political Science, Study and Teaching (Box 46)
    - Population (Box 47)
      - Michigan (Box 47)
      - Chelsea (Box 47)
      - Dearborn (Box 47)
      - Detroit (Box 47)
      - Kalamazoo (Box 47)
      - Muskegon (Box 47)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 47)
    - Poverty
      - Michigan (Box 47)
      - Relief Measures
        - Michigan (Box 47)
        - Detroit (Box 47)
    - Power Resources (Box 47)
    - Pressure Politics (Box 47)
    - Prices (Box 47)
    - Prisons -- Washtenaw County (Box 47)
    - Public Administration -- Study and Teaching (Box 47)
    - Public Assistance (Box 47)
    - Public Employees -- Labor Relations (Box 47)
    - Public Health
      - Michigan (Box 47)
      - Detroit (Box 47)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 47)
    - Public Lands (Box 48)
    - Public Opinion
      - Michigan (Box 48)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 48)
    - Public Personnel
      - Michigan (Box 48)
      - Labor Relations (Box 48)
    - Public Safety Departments (Box 48)
    - Public Schools (Box 48)
    - Public Utilities (Box 48)
    - Public Welfare
      - Michigan (Box 48)
      - Detroit (Box 48)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 48)
      - Wayne County (Box 48)
    - Public Works (Box 48)
    - Purchasing Methods -- Municipal -- Ann Arbor (Box 48)
    - Racing (Box 48)
    - Real Property -- Ann Arbor (Box 48)
    - Records Management -- Ann Arbor (Box 48)
    - Recreation (Box 48)
    - Refuse and Refuse Disposal
      - Michigan (Box 48)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 48)
      - Detroit (Box 48)
    - Regional Government (Box 48)
    - Regional Planning, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Rents (Box 48)
    - Research (Box 48)
    - Riots (Box 48)
    - Salaries
      - State (Box 48)
      - Municipal (Box 48)
    - School Districts (Box 49)
      - Michigan (Box 49)
      - Detroit (Box 49)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 49)
    - School -- Michigan (Box 49)
    - Schools (Box 49)
    - Sewage Disposal (Box 49)
    - Sheriffs -- Wayne County (Box 49)
    - Social Security (Box 49)
    - Sociology -- Rural (Box 49)
    - Social Service, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Special Districts (Box 49)
    - State Aid (Box 49)
    - State Government
      - Michigan, 3 folders (Box 49)
      - Bibliography (Box 49)
    - State Planning (Box 50)
    - Statistics
      - Michigan (Box 50)
      - Detroit (Box 50)
    - Streets
      - Michigan (Box 50)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 50)
  - T-Z
    - Tax Allocations (Box 50)
    - Tax Exemptions (Box 50)
    - Taxation
      - Business (Box 50)
      - State (Box 50)
      - Local (Box 50)
      - County -- Wayne County (Box 50)
      - Business -- Michigan (Box 50)
      - Income
        - State (Box 50)
        - Municipal
          - Michigan (Box 50)
          - Ann Arbor (Box 50)
          - Detroit (Box 50)
      - Inheritance (Box 50)
      - Intangibles (Box 50)
      - Motor Fuels (Box 50)
      - Motor Vehicles (Box 50)
      - Property (Box 51)
      - Sales
        - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 51)
        - Ann arbor (Box 51)
    - Teachers (Box 51)
    - Television Relay Systems
      - Michigan (Box 51)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 51)
    - Tourist Trade (Box 51)
    - Township Government
      - Michigan (Box 51)
      - Alaidon Township (Ingham County) (Box 51)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 51)
    - Township Planning (Box 51)
    - Trade Areas (Box 51)
    - Traffic Regulations (Box 51)
    - Traffic Survey (Box 51)
    - Training (Box 51)
    - Transportation
      - Ann Arbor (Box 51)
      - Detroit (Box 51)
    - Travel Folders (Box 51)
    - Unemployment-Detroit (Box 52)
    - Unemployment Compensation (Box 52)
    - U. S. Congress (Box 52)
    - Vocational Education (Box 52)
    - Volunteer Services (Box 52)
    - Voting
      - Michigan (Box 52)
      - Detroit (Box 52)
    - War Veterans (Box 52)
    - Water Supply
      - Michigan (Box 52)
      - Detroit Metropolitan Area (Box 52)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 52)
      - Huron River Valley (Box 52)
      - Kalamazoo County and Muskegon (Box 52)
      - Plymouth (Box 52)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 52)
    - Waterways, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Women (Box 53)
    - Workmen's Compensation (Box 53)
    - Youth Problems (Box 53)
    - Zoning
      - Michigan (Box 53)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 53)
      - Detroit (Box 53)
      - Washtenaw County (Box 53)
- Student Papers
  - Andrews, Richard D. (Box 54)
    - Our State Legislators 1949 (Box 54)
    - Standing Committees in the Michigan Legislature 1949 (Box 54)
  - Applegate, Albert A.
    - Legislative Apportionment in Michigan 1951 (Box 54)
  - Beck, Robert E. and Bulemore, Dale W.
    - A Study of the Organization of City Council Manager Government in the State of Michigan 1949 (Box 54)
  - Beissel, Dennis
    - Supervised Field Training and the Michigan Municipal League 1966 (Box 54)
  - Bentley, John P.
    - Investment of Public Retirement Systems Funds: Implementing Constitutional Provisions through Legislative Action 1965 (Box 54)
    - Uniform Accounting and Auditing in Michigan Municipalities 1965 (Box 54)
  - Berlin, Neal
    - The Michigan City Manager in Council Proceedings 1960 (Box 54)
  - Berrodin, Eugene F.
    - Report of Field Training: Employee Compensation Plan 1968 (Box 54)
    - Report of Field Training: Position Classification Plan 1968 (Box 54)
  - Betlock, Barry
    - The Present State of the Underground, circa 1968 (Box 54)
  - Bockian, J. Bernard
    - A Guide to the Operation of Tax Sales in the State of Michigan 1956 (Box 54)
  - Boothby, Bryce
    - Public Employee Relations in Michigan 1951 (Box 54)
  - Branch, Richard
    - Field Training Report, after 1966 (Box 54)
  - Brand, Jone E.
    - A Centralized Purchasing System for Sturgis 1960 (Box 54)
  - Brinkman, Mrs. Helen P.
    - Group Insurance Coverage at the University of Michigan 1951 (Box 54)
  - Buckley, Frederick J.
    - State Income Taxes: Analysis of Constitutional Problems and Statutory Provisions in Michigan and Selected States 1950 (Box 54)
  - Cargo, David
    - The Republican Party in Michigan 1953 (Box 54)
  - Cartwright, John
    - How to Prepare a Municipal Employee Handbook 1960 (Box 54)
  - Chiang, Jan-Kwei
    - Park Washtenaw Compromise (a supervised Field Training report) 1964 (Box 54)
  - Cloutier, Daniel R.
    - Aids in Revenue Estimates in Michigan 1951 (Box 54)
  - Coburn, Walter W.
    - Records Management in Michigan 1955 (Box 54)
  - Davis, Alan C. (Box 55)
    - A History of the Michigan Retail Sales Tax 1933-1953 (Box 55)
  - Davis, Frank A. C.
    - Zoning Uses and Use District Specification in Michigan Municipalities 1955 (Box 55)
  - Dell, Charles E.
    - The National Committeeman in Michigan Politics 1951 (Box 55)
  - Deppen, John P.
    - A Study of the Problem and Regulation of Moonlighting within Michigan Municipalities for the Purpose of Recommending to the City Manager a Suitable Course of Action for the City of Plymouth, Michigan 1960 (Box 55)
  - Dinell, Tom
    - The Taxation of Intangibles in Michigan 1950 (Box 55)
  - DeSantis, Ralph A.
    - Compensation of City Councilmen in Michigan: A Study of Attitudes and Opinions of City Councilmen, 1956. (Box 55)
  - DeSantis, Ralph A. and Richard A. Schwartz
    - Survey Report of the Whitmore Lake Area Study 1956 (Box 55)
  - Donaldson, John G.
    - The Use of Interim Committees in the Michigan Legislature 1943-1954, 1955 (Box 55)
  - Dossett, Robert R.
    - County Zoning in Michigan 1955 (Box 55)
  - Duston, Eugene
    - The Classification Process -- Procedures and Forms 1967 (Box 55)
  - Dykstal, Henry A.
    - The Combined Fire and Police Department of Oak Park 1956 (Box 55)
    - Management Development Activities at National Bank of Detroit and the Michigan Employment Security Commission 1961 (Box 55)
  - Eckert, Elonora
    - The Growth of Administrative Structure in Michigan 1950 (Box 55)
  - Eichstedt, John H.
    - Payments in Lieu of Taxes on Public Lands Under the Jurisdiction of the Michigan Department of Conservation 1955 (Box 55)
    - Recreational Land Requirements in the Detroit Metropolitan Area 1955 (Box 55)
  - Elumeze, John Benedict
    - A Study of the Problem of Front and Rear Vehicle License Plates in Michigan -- Together with a Survey of the Practices in the States of the Union 1955 (Box 55)
  - Exo, Warren D.
    - Methods of Keeping a Record Inventory of the State of Michigan's Real Property 1955 (Box 55)
  - Eugene, Duston
    - Position Classification Plan Prepared for the City of Ecorse, Michigan 1967 (Box 55)
    - Wages, Salary and Fringe Benefits Survey and Analysis for City of Ferndale, Michigan 1967 (Box 55)
  - Forman, Robert G.
    - The Industrial Management of Large Scale Government Programs, circa 1965 (Box 55)
  - Frisinger, Joseph A. and Robert H. Pealy
    - Comprehensive Evaluation and Review of the Development of the Rules and Regulations and the Contractual Agreement of the City of Ann Arbor and Local 369 of the International Union of the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO 1966 (Box 55)
  - Holmes, Lois Anne
    - Municipal Clerical Testing 1954 (Box 55)
  - House, Clyde V.
    - The Future of the Port of Detroit and the Significance of the St. Lawrence Seaway 1954 (Box 55)
  - Howland, Paul D.
    - Payments in Lieu of Taxes from State Colleges and Universities to Municipalities in which they Reside 1954 (Box 55)
  - Huss, John H.
    - Sales Tax Administration in Michigan 1937 (Box 55)
  - Jefferis, Thomas K. (Box 56)
    - Cooperation or Consolidation -- A Study of the Fusion Potential of Five Communities (Grosse Pointe Area) 1952 (Box 56)
  - Johnson, Mary Ruth
    - Memorandum of Field Work (Ingham and Gratiot counties) 1960 (Box 56)
  - Karris, Anita
    - The Woman's Division of the Detroit Police Department 1951 (Box 56)
  - Kelly, Michael J.
    - The Implications of Collective Bargaining -- A Study of Detroit's Budgetary Process 1968 (Box 56)
  - Krause, Robert D.
    - Increases in Numbers of Michigan State Employees Due to Legislation 1942-1949 (Box 56)
  - Laidlaw, David O.
    - A Financial Study of the Huron-Clinton Metropolitan Authority 1948 (Box 56)
  - Lavine, M.
    - The Departmental Personnel Officer and Position Classification 1948 (Box 56)
  - Ley, Mike
    - Report on Internship Activities at City Hall (Ann Arbor) 1967 (Box 56)
  - Lydens, Peter F.
    - Public Relations ad it Affects Traffic Engineering and Municipal Government (Grand Rapids) 1956 (Box 56)
  - Lydens, Peter F. and R. N. Schwartz
    - Preliminary Report on the Whitmore Lake Area Study 1955 (Box 56)
  - Magdanz, James F.
    - Wage Survey Report and Employee Classification, Grand Haven, Michigan 1947 (Box 56)
  - Martin, Eileen
    - Administration of the Youth Labor Laws in the State of Michigan 1957 (Box 56)
  - Mason, Donald L.
    - A Change in Budget Structure, Operation, and Procedures in the City of Ann Arbor, Michigan 1959 (Box 56)
  - McCauley, Paul L.
    - Financial Administration in Washtenaw County, circa 1958 (Box 56)
  - McKevittt, John G.
    - Municipal Insurance Practices (Ann Arbor) 1947 (Box 56)
    - Report of Major Municipal Developments in Michigan -- Calendar Year 1946 (Box 56)
    - Field Work Report 1946-1947 (Box 56)
  - McMurry, J. H.
    - The Administration of Tax Delinquent Lands 1948 (Box 56)
  - The Michigan University Land Use and Regional Planning Seminar
    - Land Use Problems -- The Inland Lake Belt of Southeastern Michigan 1959 (Box 56)
  - Moody, Eugene G.
    - Snow and Ice Removal Practices in Michigan Municipalities 1948 (Box 56)